{"cosmos":[{"level":"1","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm big and bright and shine so high, you see me during the day in the sky! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌞 I give you warmth."},{"text":"💛 I am very, very hot."},{"text":"😎 Plants need me to grow."}],"options":[{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"2","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm round and white and shine at night, sometimes I'm full and big and bright! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐺 Werewolves like me!"},{"text":"🧀 People think I am made of cheese"},{"text":"🌚 I change my shape."}],"options":[{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"3","type":"cosmos","question":"I am many bright lights, twinkling in the dark night! What are we?","hints":[{"text":"✨ Make a wish on us!"},{"text":"🌌 We are very far away."},{"text":"🔭 You need a telescope to see us better."}],"options":[{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Clouds","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Planets","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"4","type":"cosmos","question":"I am your home, a big round ball, where you play and stand up tall! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌳 I have trees and oceans."},{"text":"🌎 I am a planet."},{"text":"🏠 You live here."}],"options":[{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Earth","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Jupiter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"5","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm a hot and fiery thing, but I'm not the sun, what could I be?","hints":[{"text":"☄️ I fly through space"},{"text":"🔥 I burn up when I get to earth"},{"text":"🌠 I am also called a shooting star"}],"options":[{"label":"Meteor","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"6","type":"cosmos","question":"It's like a puzzle, but with stars, it makes a picture, near and far. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"ursa major 🐻"},{"text":"Orion 🏹"},{"text":"✨ People long ago used me to find their way."}],"options":[{"label":"Constellation","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Galaxy","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"7","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm big and twirly, full of stars, Earth is just a tiny part of us. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💫 We are spiral shaped"},{"text":"🌌 We contain billions of stars"},{"text":"🥛 Our name makes you think of milk."}],"options":[{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Galaxy","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Asteroid","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"8","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm a rock that flies in space, sometimes near Earth at a fast pace! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🪨 I'm smaller than a planet."},{"text":"💥 I can make a big crater if I hit Earth."},{"text":"☄️ Some people think I killed the dinosaurs."}],"options":[{"label":"Asteroid","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"9","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm a group of planets going around the sun, Earth is one of us, it's lots of fun! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☀️ The planets revolve around our star"},{"text":"🪐 Earth is the 3rd planet"},{"text":"🚀 We can explore the system with rockets."}],"options":[{"label":"Solar System","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Galaxy","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Constellation","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"10","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a very large cloud in space made of gas and dust, new stars are born in this place. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💨 I look very beautiful and colorful."},{"text":"✨ New stars are born here"},{"text":"🌌 Some are named after animals"}],"options":[{"label":"Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Nebula","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Asteroid","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}}],"food":[{"level":"1","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and you peel me. Monkeys love to eat me! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I am a favorite food of monkeys!"},{"text":"💛 My color is bright yellow."},{"text":"🖐️ You need to peel my skin off."}],"options":[{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Strawberry","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"2","type":"food","question":"I am red and round and grow on a tree. Sometimes I'm used to make juice. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌳 I grow on a tree!"},{"text":"🥤 You can make juice with me."},{"text":"🔴 My color is red."}],"options":[{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grapes","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"3","type":"food","question":"I am long and orange and bunnies love to eat me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 Bunnies like to eat me!"},{"text":"🌱 I grow in the ground."},{"text":"🧡 I am the color orange."}],"options":[{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Broccoli","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"4","type":"food","question":"I am white and cold, and you eat me with a spoon. I come in lots of flavors! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥄 You need a spoon to eat me!"},{"text":"🥶 I am very cold."},{"text":"🍦 I am a sweet treat!"}],"options":[{"label":"Yogurt","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ice Cream","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pudding","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"5","type":"food","question":"I am a small, green vegetable. I grow in a pod and you can eat me by themselves. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🟢 My color is green."},{"text":"👪 I grow with many of my friends."},{"text":"🌱 I grow in a pod."}],"options":[{"label":"Beans","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Peas","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Corn","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"6","type":"food","question":"I am made from milk and I can be hard or soft. You can put me on sandwiches. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐮 I come from a cow."},{"text":"🥪 You can put me on a sandwich."},{"text":"🧀 I am often yellow or white."}],"options":[{"label":"Yogurt","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cheese","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Butter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"7","type":"food","question":"I am round and orange and I have a lot of seeds inside. People carve me at Halloween. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🎃 People make faces on me for Halloween."},{"text":"🍂 I grow in the fall."},{"text":"🧡 My color is orange."}],"options":[{"label":"Tomato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pumpkin","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"8","type":"food","question":"I am made of dough and baked in an oven. I'm often sliced and eaten with butter. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍞 You can put butter on me."},{"text":"🔥 I am cooked in an oven."},{"text":"🌾 I am made with flour."}],"options":[{"label":"Bread","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cookies","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"9","type":"food","question":"I am a fruit with a fuzzy brown skin and green inside. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥝 I have a lot of tiny, black seeds inside."},{"text":"🇨🇳 I am originally from China."},{"text":"🟤 My skin is brown and fuzzy."}],"options":[{"label":"Avocado","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Kiwi","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"10","type":"food","question":"I am a yellow fruit, and my juice is very sour. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍋 People sometimes put me in their drinks!"},{"text":"🟡 I am the color yellow."},{"text":"😖 My juice makes you pucker your lips."}],"options":[{"label":"Lemon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mango","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pineapple","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}}]}